http://www.irvinepres.org/privacy-policy/

HOME/
ABOUT US/Who We AreWhat We BelieveWorship ServiceIPC StoriesStaffContact
Us
MINISTRIES/Children's MinistryStudent MinistriesAdult MinistryMen's MinistryWomen's MinistryBible ReadingsJenny Hart Preschool
CONNECT/Family NightDeacon CareEmail Signup
EVENTS/Upcoming EventsAll Events
OUTREACH/Local Missions: Orange CountyLocal Missions: MexicoGlobal Missions: AfricaGlobal Missions: Asia
MEDIA/Sermons
GIVE/Faith Commitment 2018Give Online
About Us
HOME/
ABOUT US/Who We AreWhat We BelieveWorship ServiceIPC StoriesStaffContact
Us
MINISTRIES/Children's MinistryStudent MinistriesAdult MinistryMen's MinistryWomen's MinistryBible ReadingsJenny Hart Preschool
CONNECT/Family NightDeacon CareEmail Signup
EVENTS/Upcoming EventsAll Events
OUTREACH/Local Missions: Orange CountyLocal Missions: MexicoGlobal Missions: AfricaGlobal Missions: Asia
MEDIA/Sermons
GIVE/Faith Commitment 2018Give Online
Privacy PolicyIrvine Presbyterian Church (“IPC”) is committed to respecting the privacy of individuals who visit the IPC website ("website"). We do use some information you provide in order to make your experience on our website better, but we recognize that this information belongs to you and we take your privacy very seriously. Unless specified otherwise, IPC will adhere to the privacy policy detailed in this statement.Application of Privacy PolicyThis privacy policy applies to all personal information submitted by users ("Users") through IPC’s website.Personal InformationIPC collects personal and non-personal information from our online users. Visitors are not required to register to view pages of our website. Non-personal information is used to track statistical information about the number of people visiting certain pages so we can improve the website experience. This information is used only for internal purposes and is not disclosed to any non-affiliated third parties.Personal information, such as name, address, and contact information, is collected so IPC can contact you. We may collect this information and other personal information when you wish to obtain goods or services from us, when you register for conferences or events, and when you participate in activities or complete other forms. IPC will not collect any personal information about visitors except when they knowingly provide it, and this information will be kept confidential and will not be disclosed to non-affiliated third parties except when required by law. IPC does not seek personal information from children online.IPC takes precautions — including administrative, technical, and physical measures — to safeguard your personal information against loss, theft, and misuse, as well as against unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, and destruction. Because the internet is not a secure medium, the privacy of communications over the internet cannot be guaranteed. IPC does not assume responsibility for any harm, loss, or damage you may incur by the sending of personal or confidential information over the internet by or to IPC.Use of Information and DataWe use the information you provide for the purposes for which it was originally collected, for example, to respond to your email or to provide the programs or services you requested. We may also use this information to help us improve the content and functionality of our website, to better understand the needs and interests of the people and organizations that use our website, and to improve our programs and services.IPC may use Google Analytics to help us gather details about the use of our websites. Google Analytics is a web analytics tool that helps website owners understand how visitors engage with their sites. Google Analytics collects information anonymously. It reports website trends without identifying individual visitors. For more information, please visithttp://www.google.com/policies/privacy/.ConsentBy accessing the website, all Users consent to the collection, use, disclosure, storage and processing of their information in accordance with this privacy policy.Credit Card Payment InformationIPC may collect credit card information in the course of business on our sites. We strive to protect the confidentiality and security of this information by maintaining safeguards to protect against the loss, misuse, or unlawful disclosure of card numbers. No credit card information is stored or logged on any system housed at IPC — the information is passed straight to our payment processors via encrypted and secure methods.Changes to Privacy PolicyIPC may amend or update this privacy policy from time to time, with or without notice to web Users. All Users agree to be bound by the privacy policy that is in effect at the time they access the website.  REFUND POLICYFor information on contributions and our refund policy, visit our Giving page.
EVENTS |
CONTACT US |
EMAIL SIGNUP |
GIVE |
PRIVACY POLICY |
CCB
© 2018 Irvine Presbyterian Church   •
4445 Alton Pkwy, Irvine, CA 92604   •   949.786.9627  •  Sunday Services:  8:30, 9:45 & 11 am
